{
    "subject": "resource/Today!_(Mississippi_John_Hurt_album)",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Vanguard_Records",
    "human_readable": "The album 'Today!' by Mississippi John Hurt is released under Vanguard Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8628759980201721,
            "question": "What is the name of the album released by Mississippi John Hurt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8433274626731873,
            "question": "Name an album by Mississippi John Hurt."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7165557146072388,
            "question": "Under which record label was 'Today!' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6988438963890076,
            "question": "Which musician released the album 'Today!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6729884743690491,
            "question": "Who released the album 'Today!'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5548440217971802,
            "question": "What record label is associated with the album 'Today!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.550288200378418,
            "question": "What genre of music is associated with Mississippi John Hurt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46326807141304016,
            "question": "Are there any notable songs on the album 'Today!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43415871262550354,
            "question": "Is 'Today!' a studio album or a live recording?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.360882431268692,
            "question": "What year was 'Today!' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The album 'Today!' by Mississippi John Hurt is released under Vanguard Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4188_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Today!' a studio album or a live recording?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4188_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable songs on the album 'Today!'",
            "html": "dbpedia_4188_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is associated with Mississippi John Hurt?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4188_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4188_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the album \"Today!\" by Mississippi John Hurt, and it mentions that it was released in 1966 by Vanguard Records. Therefore, the statement that this album is released under Vanguard Records is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about \"Today!\" being the first album of music by Mississippi John Hurt that was owned and released under Vanguard Records. Therefore, the statement \"The album 'Today!' by Mississippi John Hurt is released under Vanguard Records\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}